#### Contact

+91 9651771323 (Work) virensood11811@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/virensood-382612121 (LinkedIn)

# Viren Sood

Storyteller | Sales | IIT Kanpur Chandigarh

### Summary

Sales and storytelling go hand in hand. With 4 plus years of B2B SaaS Sales experience, I share my learnings from sales, marketing, multiple interviews & startup culture here on Linkedin in the form of daily stories.

Why to make mistakes yourself when you can learn from mine?

## Experience

Self-employed Freelance Writer June 2020 - Present (3 months) Chandigarh, India

#### GoComet

Head, Corporate Relations September 2016 - Present (4 years)

Mumbai Area, India

We are bringing international freight industry online and making it convenient and efficient for businesses to move their heavy cargo. See www.gocomet.in for the product and service

Ola (ANI Technologies Pvt. Ltd)
Marketing and Operations
July 2015 - September 2016 (1 year 3 months)

### Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Kanpur Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) · (2011 - 2015)